O Sales Enquiry/Helpline

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





SAVITHA CHINNAPPAREDDY (Featured)

Technical Lead-Lead Data Scientist seeking roles in Data Analysis, Data Visualization, Project Planning, Stakeholder Management, Client Management, Cloud Computing, Machine Learning, Python, Docker, SQL, Java, MATLAB.

Total Experience: 10 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MTech [Biomedical]

Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Designation: Technical Lead (Lead Data Scientist)

Current Company: QuEST Global Engineering Pvt. Ltd.
Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Technical Lead-Lead Data Scientist, Team Lead, Data Analysis, Data Visualization, Project

Planning, Stakeholder Management, Client Management, Cloud Computing, Machine

Learning, Python, Docker, SQL, Java, MATLAB

Verified : Chone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Acompetent professional with 10 years of rich experience Followed the project life cycle methodology defined under the process framework; ensured that customer deadlines were met within project budgets Collaborate with Architecture and infrastructure teams to implement conformant build/deploy pipelines specific to Machine Learning/Deep Learning and Analytic workloads Evaluated data findings to communicate findings in a clear, structured manner; developing cordial relations with stakeholders and rendering guidance Expertise in interpreting large-sets of data, analyzing results using statistical, deep learning tools summarized findings and presented analytics & reports to Senior Management and clients for critical decision making Provided data visualization & reporting, market/ consumer research inputs to leading clients across retail, aerospace, oil & gas & healthcare domains as per SLA's

Work Experience

QuEST Global Engineering Pvt. Ltd. as Technical Lead (Lead Data Scientist)
 Mar 2018 to Till Date

Key Result Areas:

Leading data Science Team, Training, Management, R & D for Al - ML projects, proof of concepts, providing solutions

different problem Statements in area of Machine Learning, deep learning, NLP, Speech Analytics, Data Science and Reinforcement Learning

Epictenet Private Limited as Technical Consultant (Artificial Intelligence) Jan 2018 to Mar 2018

Key Result Areas:

Developing custom Al algorithm to improve performance of the chatbot

EMICS Technologies, EMIX Technologies Private Limited as Research & Development Engineer Nov 2014 to Jan 2018

Key Result Areas:

Identifying, analyzing, and interpreting the research and development projects in hardware and software on new technologies

and transforming into multiple proposals, proof of concepts, providing training to team, technical documentation, client meetings, presentation, implementation

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2009 PG: M.Tech (Biomedical) from DSCE in 2011

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Windows, Linux, Mac	
Python, Java, R, MATLAB /NN-toolbox	
Teradata, Casandra, SQL. Cloud: AWS	
GitHub, Docker and Kube	
Tableau, Weka	
TensorFlow, keras, Scikit Learn	
NLKT, SciPy, stats-models	
PySpark , pandas , NumPy	
ML, DL frameworks, Kafka	
Al Tools	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				
Tamil				
Kannada				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.